dear: adj. 亲爱的，珍贵的；昂贵的
Lesson 19. A very dear cat. Kidnappers are rarely interested in animals. But they recently took
第19课。一只非常亲爱的猫。绑架者很少对动物感兴趣。但是他们最近接受了
considerable: adj. 相当大的, wealthy: adj. 富的，有钱的
considerable interest in Mrs. Eleanor Ramsey's cat. Mrs. Eleanor Ramsey. A very wealthy old lady
对埃莉诺·拉姆齐夫人的猫的兴趣非常兴趣。埃莉诺·拉姆西夫人。一个非常富有的老太太
orderly: adj. 有规律的
has shared a flat with her cat. Rastus. For a great many years. Rastus leads an orderly life.
与她的猫分享了一个公寓。拉斯图斯。多年来。拉斯图斯过着有序的生活。
He usually takes a short walk in the evenings and is always home by seven o'clock.
他通常在晚上步行一小段路程，总是在七点钟回家。
One evening, however, he failed to arrive. Mrs. Ramsey got very worried. She looked everywhere
但是，一个晚上，他未能到达。拉姆齐太太非常担心。她到处看
disappearance: n.   失踪
for him but could not find him. Their days after Rastus' disappearance. Mrs. Ramsey received an
对他来说，但找不到他。他们失踪后的日子。拉姆西夫人收到了
anonymous: adj. 匿名的
anonymous letter. The writer stated that Rastus was in safe hands and would be returned immediately
匿名信。作者说，拉斯图斯是安全的，将立即退还
ransom: n.   赎金
if Mrs. Ramsey paid a ransom of $1,000. Mrs. Ramsey was instructed to place the money in a
如果拉姆齐太太支付了1,000美元的赎金。拉姆齐太太被指示将钱放在
cardboard: n.   硬纸板
cardboard box and to leave it outside her door. At first she decided to go to the police.
纸板箱，将其放在她的门外。起初，她决定去警察。
But fearing that she would never see Rastus again, the letter had made that quite clear, she.
但是，她担心她再也见不到拉斯图斯，这封信已经很清楚了。
kidnapper: n.   绑架者，拐骗者
Changed her mind, she withdrew $1,000 from her bank and followed the kidnappers' instructions.
改变了主意，她从银行撤回了1,000美元，并遵循了绑架者的指示。
kidnapper: n.   绑架者，拐骗者
The next morning, the box had disappeared but Mrs. Ramsey was sure that the kidnapper would keep
第二天早上，盒子消失了，但拉姆齐太太确定绑架者会保留
punctually: adv. 准时地
his word. Sure enough, Rastus arrived punctually at seven o'clock that evening. He looked very well
他的话。果然，拉斯图斯（Rastus）当天晚上七点钟出现。他看起来很好
astound: v.   使吃惊
though he was rather thirsty. For he drank half a bottle of milk. The police were astounded when Mrs.
虽然他很渴。因为他喝了半瓶牛奶。夫人夫人时，警察感到惊讶。
dear: adj. 亲爱的，珍贵的；昂贵的
Ramsey told them what she had done. She explained that Rastus was very dear to her. Considering the
拉姆齐告诉他们她做了什么。她解释说，拉斯图斯对她很珍贵。考虑到
dear: adj. 亲爱的，珍贵的；昂贵的
amount she paid, he was dear and more ways than one.
她付的金额，他是亲爱的，而不是一种。